Finding Aid to the San Francisco Department of Public Health AIDS Office records SFH 4
San Francisco History Center, San Francisco Public Library
- Contracts and Related Documents, 1984-1993; Record Group 2; 39 Cubic Feet
  - Contracts, Series 13
    - Operations Branch: Contracts, 1990-1991; Subseries 13.4
      - Mission Neighborhood Center: CT83-10314A, 17017 S\GF (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - POC Contracts, 1988-1989; Subseries 13.5
      - Asian American Recovery Education & Research (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
      - Bayview Hunter's Point Foundation (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Catholic Charities (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - 18th Street Services (Box 38, Folder 6-7)
      - Fairbank, Bregman & Maullin
        This file was listed in the legacy finding aid but was not in the box.
      - Friendship House (Box 38, Folder 8-11)
      - HIV Day Services (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Instituto FIR (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Mission Neighborhood Health Services (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - PPHM/Operation Concern (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Early Contracts, 1986-1987; Series 14
    - AIDS Office Proposal Guidelines (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Asian American Health Forum: CT83-00308, CT83-94003, CT83-94048 (Box 38, Folder 17-19)
    - Asian American Recovery Services: CT83-94076 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Bay View Hunters Point: (for 18th Street Services) CT83-72025A (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Working Papers/Working Folders, Series 15
    - First OTS Development Files and Grants, 1987-1992; Subseries 15.1
      - Home Health Care - AV: Workpapers (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Home Health Care PHS/HRSA, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - SFAF Social Services Workpapers, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Contracts DHS / AIDS Home Health Grant (Box 39, Folder 4-8)
      - ATS Budgets & Data, 1988-1992 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Quarterly Reports, 1990-1992
        - CURAS (Box 39, Folder 10)
        - Home Care Companions (Box 39, Folder 11)
        - Maitri AIDS Hospice (Box 39, Folder 12)
        - Mission Neighborhood Health Center (Box 39, Folder 13)
        - National Task Force on AIDS (Box 39, Folder 14)
        - Shanti Project (Box 39, Folder 15)
        - San Francisco General Hospital (Box 39, Folder 16)
        - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (Box 39, Folder 17)
        - Operation Concern (Box 39, Folder 18)
        - Tenderloin AIDS Resource (Box 39, Folder 19)
        - PPMC / VNH (Box 39, Folder 20)
        - UCSF Center on Deafness (Box 39, Folder 21)
        - Walden House (Box 39, Folder 22-23)
        - Westside Community Mental Health (Box 39, Folder 24)
        - 18th Street Services (Box 39, Folder 25-26)
        - Baker Places, Inc. (Box 39, Folder 27)
      - Black Coalition on AIDS, 1990-1991
        - Request for Proposal (Box 39, Folder 28)
        - Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 29)
        - Monitoring Report (Box 39, Folder 30)
        - Quarterly Report (Box 39, Folder 31)
      - Catholic Charities, 1990-1991
        - Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 32)
        - Quarterly Report (Box 39, Folder 33)
        - Monitoring Report (Box 39, Folder 34)
      - UCSF / Urban Health Study CT83-07069 (Box 39, Folder 35)
      - AIDS Grant Women's Institute for Mental Health (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - First Prevention Efforts funded by CDC, 1985-1987; Subseries 15.2
      - CDC/CPS Education /Risk Rededuction Program (Box 40, Folder 1-3)
      - CDC Application for PHS (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - PHS Deminstration Workpapers (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - CDC Test-linked Counseling 6/86 Workpapers (Box 40, Folder 6-8)
      - CDC/CPS Com Demo Project Workpapers, October 1985-September 1986 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Risk Reduction, October 1996-September 1986 (Box 40, Folder 10-12)
      - CDC/CPS AIDS Information Education (Project 247) Renewal, February 1986-February 1987 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - CDC - ATS "Did Not Materialize", March 1986-March 1987 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - CDC/PC ATS, March 1985 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - CDC/Previous Services AIDS Antibody Testing GRANT, March 1985 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Working Papers, 1987-1989; Subseries 15.3
      - Shanti Project:
        - Review (Box 41, Folder 1)
        - Loose Papers (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - SFAF:Education
        - Ad Valorem: Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 3)
        - Ad Valorem: Workpapers (Box 41, Folder 4)
        - State Information & Education: Workpapers (Box 41, Folder 5)
        - State Information & Education: Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 6)
        - State Block GRANT: Workpapers (Box 41, Folder 7)
        - State Block GRANT: Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 8)
        - Alternative Test Site: Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 9)
        - Alternative Test Site: Workpapers (Box 41, Folder 10)
        - Social Services: Workpapers (Box 41, Folder 11)
        - Social Services: Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 12)
        - Federal 254: Workpapers (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Instituto Familiar de la Raza: Workpapers (Box 41, Folder 14-18)
      - Multicultural Prevention Resource Center: Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Home Health Pacific Presbyterian Medical Center: Workpapers (Box 41, Folder 20-21)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (Box 41, Folder 22-23)
      - Mission Neighborhood Health Center. Workpapers, Correspondence. APFUC (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Operation Concern:
        - Workpapers. GF (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence. GF (Box 42, Folder 3)
        - Notes. GF (Box 42, Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous. GF (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - PPMC/Visiting Nurses Hospice:
        - Workpapers. GF/HRSA (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence. GF/HRSA (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation/Client Services:
        - Workpapers. GF (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - Correspondence. GF (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF)/Education:
        - Correspondence. GF/Block/CDC (Box 42, Folder 10)
        - Workpapers. GF/Block/CDC (Box 42, Folder 11)
        - '89. GF/Block/CDC (Box 42, Folder 12)
        - Notes. GF/Block/CDC (Box 42, Folder 13)
        - Workpapers. STATE I&E (Box 42, Folder 14)
        - CorrespondenceSTATE I&E (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - Shanti:
        - Workpapers. General Funds (Box 42, Folder 16)
        - Correspondence. General Funds (Box 42, Folder 17)
        - Workingpapers '89. General Funds (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - Women's Institute:
        - Working papers. STATE I&E (Box 42, Folder 19)
        - Correspondence. STATE I&E (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF) Education Outreach Proposal '88 (Box 42, Folder 21)
      - SFAF Programs Proposal '88/89 (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - SFAF Contract (Rejected) (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - Cross Cultural Training for AIDS Service Providers (Box 42, Folder 24)
      - AIDS Indigent Direct Services (Box 42, Folder 25-37)
    - Operations Branch. Contracts, 1989-1993; Subseries 15.5
      - 18th Street Services: Youth Prev. STATE (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Asian American Recovery Services (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Bayview-Hunters Point Foundation (BVHPF)
        - 83-17131 CAREIA (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - 83-17148-17149 CDC (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - 83-17158,A CARE II & 1 (Box 43, Folder 5)
        - 83-17161 CARE 1B (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - 83-20303A,33006 B/GF (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - Street Outreach 83-27074 CARE 1B (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Black Coalition on AIDS
        - CARE 1B (Box 43, Folder 9)
        - GF (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - California Pacific Medical Center
        - VNH 83-17070 CARE 1A (Box 43, Folder 11)
        - 83-17073,A CARE 1A, & 1Bi (Box 43, Folder 12)
        - 83-20307 GF (Box 43, Folder 13)
        - Pacific Presbyterian Medical Center / INH P-S Support 83-07151 CARE 1(B) (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Planned ParenthoodlEIRC (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF)
        - P-S Support 83-10317,10317A GF (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - EIRC,CDC 83-10330 GF (Box 43, Folder 17)
        - SFAF. Community Consortium (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - CAL-PEP, Tri-prtite GF (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - Project Inform / EACH: Clinical Trials Advocacy CARE I (A) (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - SHANTI:
        - Crossings 83-17104 CARE 1(A) (Box 43, Folder 21)
        - 83-07138 CARE 1(A) (Box 43, Folder 22)
      - UCSF AIDS Health Project:
        - State ATS 83-17011 STATE (Box 43, Folder 23)
        - EIRC/CPC 83-10336 GF (Box 43, Folder 24)
      - UCSF Center for Positive Care 83-00337, 10306,A, 17064. COPY ONLY, GF (Box 43, Folder 25)
      - UCSF / NTFAP CAL-PEP (EIRC) (Box 43, Folder 26)
      - UCSF / Urban Health Study 83-07069A CDC (Box 43, Folder 27)
      - Women's Institute for Mental Health 83-10356,17050 GF & STATE (Box 43, Folder 28)
      - UCSF / AHP / PREV EDUC (ATS) 83-00318/94013 CDC & HRSA (Box 43, Folder 29)
      - City & County of San Francisco, Department of Public Health, AIDS Office, AIDS Education & Prevention Grant Application (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Operations Branch. Contracts. Working Folders, 1991-1993; Subseries 15.5
      - Cal-Pep CT83-20306 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Catholic Charities CT-17086, CT83-2709 (Box 44, Folder 2-3)
      - Central City Hospitality House CT83-20347 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Community United in Response to AIDS SIDA CT83-17169 (Box 44, Folder 5-7)
      - Family Service Agency: Contract FY91-92. Correspondence, Reports, Care Monitoring 11-91 (Box 44, Folder 8-11)
      - Filipino Task Force On AIDS. 83-17076. CDC (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - GAPA Community HIV Project. 83-17160. CARE II (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - GAPA Community HIV Project. 83-17074. CARE 1B (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Genesis Church Ecumenical. 83-17090. CARE 1A (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - GAPA HIV Project. 83-17192,20302, 33017B. CDC & GF (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Golden Gate Comm. Inc. 83-17133. CARE IA (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - Haight Ashbury Free Medical Center. 83-27087,A. CDC (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - Hartford Street Zen Center. 83-17119. CARE IB (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - Health Outreach Team. 83-17082. CARE IA (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - Instituto Familiar de La Raza. 83-17107. CARE IA (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - Instituto Familiar de La Raza. 83-27078. CDC (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - Larkin Street Center. 83-17120. CARE IB (Box 44, Folder 23)
      - Mission Neighborhood Health Center/Trials, Administration. 83-17187. CARE 1B (Box 44, Folder 24)
      - National Task Force on AIDS/Prevention. 83-20350, 83-33025B. GF (Box 44, Folder 25-26)
      - Professional Management and Development. 83-27081,27051. STATE & CARE 1B (Box 44, Folder 27)
      - Rose Resnick for the Blind (Box 44, Folder 28)
      - St. Mary's Hospital/Medical. 83-17096. CARE 1B (Box 44, Folder 29)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation. 83-17170.CARE II (Box 44, Folder 30)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation. 83-17183. CDC (Box 44, Folder 31)
      - SFAF Spanish. 83-20321,A. GF (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - SFAF. Tri-Partite. 83-20322,A,27038. GF (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - SFAF Latino Case Mgmt. 83-27083,27084. CARE IB (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - SFAF. HIV Prevo Proj. 83-20353. GF (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - SF Network Ministry. 83-20312,A,33039,B. GF (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - SHANTI: Latino/Gay Youth Housing. 83-17093,A. CARE 1 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - SHANTI: Crossings. 83-17118,A,B. CARE IB (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - SHANTI: Practical Supp.83-20323,A,27057. GF&STATE (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - UCSF: Center on Deafness. 83-17081 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - UCSF: Urban Health Study. 83-17144 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - UCSF: Center on Deafuess. 83-17171 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - UCSF: AHP (ATS Ct.). 83-17124, 83-27079,A,27082 (Box 45, Folder 12-13)
      - Women's Inst. for Mental Health / IRIS. 83-27053 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - AIDS Health Project 83-17011 (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - AIDS Health Project 83-10336 GF (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - AIDS Health Project 83-00340,07140 CARE-F (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - AIDS Health Project 83-10306A,00337A GF (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - AIDS Health Project 83-17064 CDC (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - AIDS Health Project 83-00337 GF (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - AIDS Health Project 83-07136 CARE-S (Box 45, Folder 21)
      - AIDS Health Project 83-07110 CARE-F (Box 45, Folder 22)
      - UCSF/Urban Health Study 83-07069A CDC (Box 45, Folder 23)
      - Women's Inst For Mental Health 83-10356 GF (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Operations Branch, Working Folders. National Association of Black and White Men Together (NABWMT), 1990-1991; Subseries 15.6
      - National Association of Black and White Men Together CT83-10324A (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - NABWMT: CT83-07091 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - California Pacific Medical Center (CPMC) VNH: CT83-07135 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - California Pacific Medical Center (CPMC) OC: CT83-07132 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - CPMC: CT83-07151 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - CPMC: CT83-07160 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Planned Parenthood: CT83-17037A (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF) (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Asian American Health Forum (AAHF) / GAPA: CT83-17040 CARE-II (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Asian American Health Forum/FTF: CT83-07143 CARE-S (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Asian American Health Forum CT83-10320A, 17004 GF (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Bay View Hunters Point Found / AIAI: CT83-00338 GF (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - BVHP Found: CT83-10334 GF (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - BVHP Found: CT83-10355 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - BVHP Found:CT83-10339 GF (Box 46, Folder 15)
      - BVHP Found: CT83-07155 (Box 46, Folder 16)
      - BVHP Found CT83-07155 STATE (Box 46, Folder 17)
      - BVHPFound: CT83-10346 GF (Box 46, Folder 18)
      - BVHPFound: CT83-07137 CARE-S (Box 46, Folder 19)
      - Black Coalition On AIDS: CT83-1 0311 A, B; 10321 A, B GF (Box 46, Folder 20)
      - CAL-PEP: CT83-00331,10301 GF (Box 46, Folder 21)
      - California Pacific Medical Center (CPMC) /I Operation Concern: CT83-10344,07154 STATE (Box 46, Folder 22)
      - CPMC/VNH: CT83-10315A GF (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Contract Development Files, Series 16
    - Contract Development Files, 1986-1991; Subseries 16.1
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation Education. GF/Block/CDC. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - SFAF Client Services. General Funds. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Pacic Presbyterian Medical Center, Visiting Nurses Hospice. Gen. F/HRSA. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Operation Concern. GF. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Mission Neighborhood Health Center: APFUC. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Instituto Familiar. STATE I&E. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - IFIR: Block / CDC. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Friendship House: STATE I&E. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Friendship House: CDC. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - 18th Street Services: STATE I&E. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Catholic Charities: STATE RAS. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Bay View Hunters Point Fdn: Gen. Funds. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Bay View Hunters Point Fdn: CDCINIDA. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - Asian American Recovery Services: General Funds. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - Asian American Recovery Services: CDC/HRSA. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - Asian American Recovery Services: CDC/ Asian Survey. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - American Indian AIDS Institute: STATE I&E. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - American Indian AIDS Institute: CDC. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - Report: Education Services for Minorities. Programming Report (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - Shanti Project: AV ('87/88) Monitoring Reports (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - SFAF Education - AV. Monitoring Reports (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - SFAF Education - STATE I&E. Monitoring Reports (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - SFAF Social Services. Monitoring Reports (Box 47, Folder 23-24)
      - SFAF (Box 47, Folder 25)
      - Filipino A.A.H.F. Contract Package (Box 47, Folder 26)
      - Filipino A.A.H.F. Working Papers (Box 47, Folder 27)
      - Genesis Church (Box 47, Folder 28-29)
      - Glide (Box 47, Folder 30-32)
      - Haight Ashbury Free Clinics (Box 47, Folder 33)
      - Latino Family Alcoholism Counseling Center LAFCC (Box 47, Folder 34)
      - Mission Neighborhood Health Center (Box 47, Folder 35)
      - Pacific Presbyterian Medical Center - Visiting Nurses (Box 47, Folder 36)
      - Pacific Presbyterian Medical Center - Contract in Process (Box 47, Folder 37)
      - Pacific Presbyterian Medical Center - Visiting Nurses Contract Package (Box 47, Folder 38)
      - National Association of Black and White Men Together (Box 47, Folder 39-40)
      - Operation Concern Contract Package (Box 47, Folder 41)
      - Operation Concern Working Papers (Box 47, Folder 42)
      - Health Services:
        - HRSA Demo Project Augmentation (Box 48, Folder 1)
        - Work papers for CDC/CIDA Education GRANT 2-15-85 (Box 48, Folder 2)
        - Work papers for DPH CDC/CPS Coop. Agreement (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Prevention Grant Planning Documents:
        - PHS Plan for Prevention & Control ofAIDS (Box 48, Folder 4)
        - CDC Public Education Material Review (Box 48, Folder 5-13)
        - Shanti Project Monitoring (Box 48, Folder 14)
        - AIDS Office Monitoring Schedule (Box 48, Folder 15)
        - Budget Summary Report, Materials Request (Box 48, Folder 16)
        - San Francisco Request for Application for Information & Education on AIDS Project (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - First Contract Development Files, Subseries 16.2
      - AHP: SA AV Workpapers (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - AHP: Min ATS - Fed. Proj. 254/87-8 Workpapers (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - 87-8 Asian American Recovery Services: Asian/Pacific lslander Survey Project 254 Workpapers (Box 49, Folder 3-6)
      - Bay View Hunters Point -MAPA: Ad valorem Workpapers (Box 49, Folder 7-8)
      - Bay View Hunters Point -MAPA: STATE I&E Workpapers (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Friendship House '87-88 Block Grant, 465 Workingpapers (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Instituto Familiar de la Raza: Ad valorem 87-8 Workingpapers (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Instituto Familiar STATE I & E 87-8 Workingpapers (Box 49, Folder 12-13)
      - 87-8 Prevention Education IF/R - Latino AIDS Project (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - 87-8 Operation Concern: Workingpapers (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Health Services Contract Development & Monitoring Files, 1987-1990; Subseries 16.3
      - Shanti Financial Reports 88/89 (Box 49, Folder 16)
      - Shanti Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - AIDS Health Project Monitoring (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - AIDS Health Project Monitoring 87/88 (Box 49, Folder 19)
      - AIDS Health Proj Correspondence 88/89 (Box 49, Folder 20)
      - AIDS Health Proj Monitoring (Box 49, Folder 21)
      - Pacific Presbyterian Medical Center 88-89: Monitoring Materials (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - Garden Sullivan: Monitoring 88/89, Program Report 89/90, Program Reports 88/89 (Box 49, Folder 23-26)
      - Shanti Project
        - Monitoring 88/89 (Box 49, Folder 27)
        - Monitoring (Box 49, Folder 28)
        - Monitoring Materials (Box 49, Folder 29)
      - Hospices Financial Report 89/90 (Box 49, Folder 30)
      - Hospice (VNH) Monitoring 88/89 (Box 49, Folder 31)
      - Hospice Program Reports 88/89 (Box 49, Folder 32)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation
        - Program Report (Box 49, Folder 33)
        - Monitoring 88/89 (Box 49, Folder 34)
        - Monitoring Materials (Box 49, Folder 35)
      - Shanti Program Report 88/89 (Box 49, Folder 36)
      - Visiting Nurses Monitoring (Box 49, Folder 37)
      - PPMC Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 38-39)
    - POC Agencies: Contract Development Files & Monitoring, 1988-1990; Subseries 16.4
      - AO Sole Source/Bid Schedule 89-94 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - 88-9: RFPs (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - American Indian AIDS Institute CDC Control Process Doc. (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - AlAI STATE I&E (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Asian Amer. Rec. Services: CDC /Asian Survey CDC (Box 50, Folder 5-6)
      - AIDS Health Project: 1989-90 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - AIDS Health Project: Educational Material 1989-90 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - ASIAN AIDS Project 1989-90 (Box 50, Folder 9-12)
      - American Indians (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - Operation Concern:Contracts 89-90 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Operation Concern (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - 18th Street Services. Correspondence 1989-90 (Box 50, Folder 16-17)
      - Latino AIDS Project
        - Reports 1989-90 (Box 50, Folder 18)
        - Monitoring Protocol 1989-90 (Box 50, Folder 19)
        - Contract 1989-90 (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - Instituto Familiar
        - Reports 1989-90 (Box 50, Folder 21)
        - Monitoring Protocol 1989-90 (Box 50, Folder 22)
        - Correspondence 1989-90 (Box 50, Folder 23)
      - 88-90 DHS AIDS Community Education I Prevention RFP (Box 50, Folder 24)
      - 88-89 STATE SNAP Grant (Special Needs & Priorities) (Box 50, Folder 25)
      - 90-91 STATE Early Intervention Center (EIC) (Box 50, Folder 26)
      - 88-89 STATE AIDS Prevention & Followup Center (Box 50, Folder 27)
      - STATE Guidelines: Comprehensive HIV Education, Information & Training Programs (Box 50, Folder 28)
      - 87-8 DHS I & E Contract (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Working Papers and Contract Development Files (early), circa 1988-1989; Subseries 16.5
      - Instituto Familiar
        - Contract Proc.Docs: Block/CDC (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - Contract(s) (Box 51, Folder 2)
        - Loose reports, Contracts (Box 51, Folder 3)
        - Contr. Proc.Docs. STATE I&E (Box 51, Folder 4)
        - STATE I&E (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF) / Client Services General Fund (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - SFAF / Education GF / Block / CDC (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - SFAF / Education STATE 1& E (Box 51, Folder 8-9)
      - SFAF / Client Services (Box 51, Folder 10-11)
      - SFAF / Education (Box 51, Folder 12-13)
      - Youth Environment (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - Women's Institute for Mental Health (Box 51, Folder 15)
      - Shanti Discrimination Complaint (5/88) (Box 51, Folder 16)
      - SFAF CT83-84063 General Fund / Block (Box 51, Folder 17)
      - SFAF (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - ERIC (CPC) Contract Development, Subseries 16.6
      - Center for Positive Care (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - GMOC/EACH:Early Intervention Advocacy GF, July 1, 1991 - June 30, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 2)
        - Contract Notes (Box 52, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 4)
        - Quart. Reports (Box 52, Folder 5)
        - Monitoring Report (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Haight Ashbury Free Clinic: Substance Abuse Linkage (EIRC) GF, September 1, 1991 - June 30, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 7)
        - Contract Notes (Box 52, Folder 8)
        - Quarterly Reports (Box 52, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 10)
        - Monitoring Report (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Planned Parenthood / PHREDA Linkage / Education (EIRC) GF, September 1991-June 1992 (Box 52, Folder 12)
        - Contract Notes (Box 52, Folder 13)
        - Quarterly Reports (Box 52, Folder 14)
        - Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 15)
        - Monitoring Reports (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - SFAF: Clinical Trials (EIRC) GF, December 1991-June 1992 (Box 52, Folder 17)
        - Contract Notes (Box 52, Folder 18)
        - Quart. Reports (Box 52, Folder 19)
        - Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 20)
        - Monitoring Reports (Box 52, Folder 21)
      - Bay View Hunters Point Foundation: General Funds Workpapers (Box 52, Folder 22)
        - Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 23)